http://www.dripirrigation.com/privacy-policy

Featured ProductsTimers
Bluetooth TimersOutlet Powered (AC)Battery Powered (DC)Solar Powered (Sun)Hose Faucet ConnectionPropagationValve Accessories & PartsValves OnlyValve Manifolds
Single ZoneMultiple Zones
Water Connections
Valves
ValvesValve Accessories & Parts
Valve Assemblies
Multiple ZonesSingle Zone
Pressure RegulatorsPressure GaugesBackflow DevicesPVC RisersGarden Hose ConnectionsBall ValvesSprinkler Riser Adapters
Filters
3/4" Filters1" Filters1-1/2" Filters2" FiltersFilter Screens & Accessories
Tubing
1/2" Tube
.700 OD (most common).620 OD.710 OD
1/4" Microtube1/8" MicrotubePre-Cut Microtube
1/4" Pre-Cut Microtube1/8" Pre-Cut Microtube
1/4" Poly Risers1/2" Drip Line
17mm Check Valve Drip Line16mm Black17mm Brown
1/4" Drip LineDrip Tape3/4" Tube1" Tube
Fittings
1/8"1/4"1/2"
.700 O.D..620 O.D..710 O.D.
16mm Barbed Fittings17mm Barbed Fittings3/4"1"Drip Tape FittingsBall ValvesWashers & Screen Washers
Tools & Stakes
1/4" & 1/8" Stakes1/2" StakesPunches & Cutters1/4" Barb Insertion ToolOther ToolsTrellis Clips & "C" ClampsSprinkler Riser AdaptersAir Vacuum Relief & Flush Valves
Drippers
Pressure CompensatingNon-CompensatingNon-Draining & Check ValveTake apartStake mountedAdjustableSprinkler Riser ManifoldsSpot SpittersMulti-OutletDrip Tape1/2" Drip Line
17mm Check Valve Drip Line17mm Brown16mm Black
1/4" Drip Line
Sprinklers & Misters
Micro-Sprinklers
Fixed FlowAdjustable FlowFixed Spray PatternAdjustable Spray PatternPop-Up Micro-SprinklersParts & Accessories
Micro-Sprinkler Assemblies
Sprinkler, Stake & MicrotubeSprinklers & 1/2" BasesMicrotube AssembliesClose-Outs / Discontinued
DAN Sprinkler Products
Individual PartsNozzles & Anti-mistSpinners & SpreadersFoggersComplete Sprinkler AssembliesMicrotubing Assemblies
Hanging / Inverted Micro-Sprinklers
Complete AssembliesMicrotubing AssembliesInverted Systems Flow Controls
Foggers & Misters
Complete AssembliesFogger & Mister HeadsSystem Parts
Pre-Cut 1/4" MicrotubingSpot SpittersHome Cooling
Kits
Drip KitsVegetable Garden KitsRaised Bed KitsMisting KitsMicrosprinkler KitsDrip & Microsprinkler KitsAutomated KitsGravity Feed KitsSprinkler Riser Retrofit KitsValve Assemblies
Multiple ZonesSingle Zone
Fertilizer Injectors
EZ Flo Fertilizer Injectors
Accessories & Parts
Dosatron
PVC Fittings
Flexible Tubing For PVCAdaptersBall ValvesCrossesCouplersElbowsEnd CapsNipplesPVC RisersReducersTeesReducing TeesUnions
Greenhouse
Emitters / Single & Multi-Outlet
Single & Multi-Outlet Emitters12 Outlet ManifoldsNon-Draining & Check Valve
Micro-Sprinklers
Fixed FlowAdjustable FlowFixed Spray PatternAdjustable Spray PatternParts & Accessories
Micro-Sprinkler Assemblies
Sprinklers on 1/2" BasesMicrotube AssembliesClose-Outs / Discontinued
DAN Sprinkler Products
System PartsNozzles & Anti-MistSpinners & SpreadersComplete Sprinkler AssembliesMicro-Tube Assemblies
Hanging / Inverted Micro-Sprinklers
Complete AssembliesMicro-Tubing AssembliesInverted Systems Flow Controls
Foggers & Misters
Complete AssembliesFogger & MistersSystem Parts
Pre-Cut 1/4" & 1/8" Micro-Tube
HydroponicsGarden CenterSeasonal SpecialsSale ItemsBlack Friday SaleCyber Monday Sale
Selling Online Since 1996
Free ShippingOn Orders Over $125Find Out More Here
877-597-1669Questions? Call Us!
Over 1,000 Products IN STOCK!
Family Owned & Operated
Timers
Bluetooth TimersOutlet Powered (AC)Battery Powered (DC)Solar Powered (Sun)Hose Faucet ConnectionPropagationValve Accessories & PartsValves OnlyValve Manifolds
Single ZoneMultiple Zones
Water Connections
Valves
ValvesValve Accessories & Parts
Valve Assemblies
Multiple ZonesSingle Zone
Pressure RegulatorsPressure GaugesBackflow DevicesPVC RisersGarden Hose ConnectionsBall ValvesSprinkler Riser Adapters
Filters
3/4" Filters1" Filters1-1/2" Filters2" FiltersFilter Screens & Accessories
Tubing
1/2" Tube
.700 OD (most common).620 OD.710 OD
1/4" Microtube1/8" MicrotubePre-Cut Microtube
1/4" Pre-Cut Microtube1/8" Pre-Cut Microtube
1/4" Poly Risers1/2" Drip Line
17mm Check Valve Drip Line16mm Black17mm Brown
1/4" Drip LineDrip Tape3/4" Tube1" Tube
Fittings
1/8"1/4"1/2"
.700 O.D..620 O.D..710 O.D.
16mm Barbed Fittings17mm Barbed Fittings3/4"1"Drip Tape FittingsBall ValvesWashers & Screen Washers
Tools & Stakes
1/4" & 1/8" Stakes1/2" StakesPunches & Cutters1/4" Barb Insertion ToolOther ToolsTrellis Clips & "C" ClampsSprinkler Riser AdaptersAir Vacuum Relief & Flush Valves
Drippers
Pressure CompensatingNon-CompensatingNon-Draining & Check ValveTake apartStake mountedAdjustableSprinkler Riser ManifoldsSpot SpittersMulti-OutletDrip Tape1/2" Drip Line
17mm Check Valve Drip Line17mm Brown16mm Black
1/4" Drip Line
Sprinklers & Misters
Micro-Sprinklers
Fixed FlowAdjustable FlowFixed Spray PatternAdjustable Spray PatternPop-Up Micro-SprinklersParts & Accessories
Micro-Sprinkler Assemblies
Sprinkler, Stake & MicrotubeSprinklers & 1/2" BasesMicrotube AssembliesClose-Outs / Discontinued
DAN Sprinkler Products
Individual PartsNozzles & Anti-mistSpinners & SpreadersFoggersComplete Sprinkler AssembliesMicrotubing Assemblies
Hanging / Inverted Micro-Sprinklers
Complete AssembliesMicrotubing AssembliesInverted Systems Flow Controls
Foggers & Misters
Complete AssembliesFogger & Mister HeadsSystem Parts
Pre-Cut 1/4" MicrotubingSpot SpittersHome Cooling
Kits
Drip KitsVegetable Garden KitsRaised Bed KitsMisting KitsMicrosprinkler KitsDrip & Microsprinkler KitsAutomated KitsGravity Feed KitsSprinkler Riser Retrofit KitsValve Assemblies
Multiple ZonesSingle Zone
Fertilizer Injectors
EZ Flo Fertilizer Injectors
Accessories & Parts
Dosatron
PVC Fittings
Flexible Tubing For PVCAdaptersBall ValvesCrossesCouplersElbowsEnd CapsNipplesPVC RisersReducersTeesReducing TeesUnions
Greenhouse
Emitters / Single & Multi-Outlet
Single & Multi-Outlet Emitters12 Outlet ManifoldsNon-Draining & Check Valve
Micro-Sprinklers
Fixed FlowAdjustable FlowFixed Spray PatternAdjustable Spray PatternParts & Accessories
Micro-Sprinkler Assemblies
Sprinklers on 1/2" BasesMicrotube AssembliesClose-Outs / Discontinued
DAN Sprinkler Products
System PartsNozzles & Anti-MistSpinners & SpreadersComplete Sprinkler AssembliesMicro-Tube Assemblies
Hanging / Inverted Micro-Sprinklers
Complete AssembliesMicro-Tubing AssembliesInverted Systems Flow Controls
Foggers & Misters
Complete AssembliesFogger & MistersSystem Parts
Pre-Cut 1/4" & 1/8" Micro-Tube
Hydroponics
Privacy Policy
The Drip Store, Inc. is very sensitive to our customers’ concerns about a safe and secure shopping experience. We also understand our customers' worries about what happens to personal information given while ordering online. With this in mind, we have adopted the following privacy policy.All information supplied to us by customers will be used according to the following rules.We will NOT give, sell, trade, lend, lease or divulge any customer information to any other company, entity or individual except where/when required by U.S. federal or state law.We will NOT contact you by any means (Electronic, phone or land based) unless it concerns your order, product return or credit card used for a purchase. Only customers who have requested to be contacted about special promotions will receive solicitations from us. Customers requesting to receive solicitations from us will only receive the solicitations from The Drip Store, Inc.We may and will use your personal information within our own company (The Drip Store, Inc.) to help us understand our customers needs. The results will be for internal use only.We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.We store and reveal only the first and last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide advanced features.If you have any questions or concerns please contact us at 877-597-1669
Store Information
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Shipping Policy
Site Map
Company Information
About Us
Copyright © 2019 - The Drip Store - All Rights Reserved - The Drip Store is a registered trademark
The Drip Store
221 E. Willis Rd. Ste 7Chandler, AZ 85286
Please wait
